This is all well and good, but what we ultimately want
这些都很不错 但我们最终 想要达到的目标是
to do is have some sort of live data that our app will understand.
做出某种能够让应用理解的 实时数据
To continue our analogy with drive through data, we're going to use an API
继续之前讲到的类比 “得来速”数据 我们要使用一个 API
to allow our app to request and consume data from the USGS site as it's needed.
从而让应用可以根据需要请求并使用 来自 USGS 站点的数据
Let's take a look at the For Developers section on the left and
我们来看左侧的开发人员 (For Developers) 部分
select API Documentation.
选择 API 文档 (API Documentation)
This documentation exists to help us understand how to build the proper URL
设立此文档是为了帮助我们了解 如何构建正确的 URL
to query the site for the particular type of data that we want.
查询站点以获取某一种 想要的数据类型
Right at the top, the documentation is telling us that the URL we need to
在顶部 文档在这里写明了 我们需要查询的 URL
query is right here and then it gives us two more components at the end.
然后 在末尾处给出了 另两个成分
It went to method and actually some parameters.
会转到方法 还有 一些参数
The list of valid methods is right here below the URL and
这一部分是有效方法的列表 位于 URL 下方
we've got various options most of which are concerned with retrieving metadata
有很多选项 其中大部分方法 都用于检索有关
about the API itself.
API 本身的元数据
Scrolling down a bit though and find one called query,
向下滚动 找到名为查询 (query) 的方法
which is probably the method used to submit data requests and
这就应该是用于提交 数据请求的方法
the description does say, to submit a data request.
这里的定义也说明它可以用于提交 数据请求
Next, we have the available query parameters.
接下来 是可用的 查询参数
The first one specifies how we like USGS to format the data it sends us.
第一个参数指定 USGS 向我们发送 数据时使用的格式
We'll talk about this more shortly and then we've got query parameters for
相关内容稍后会详细讨论 然后 我们还有关于
what time period we're interested in and lots of ways to pull up the location and
感兴趣时间段的查询参数 还有提取位置的多种方式
other ways to constrain the results, such as limiting the number of results
以及其他约束结果的方式 例如 限制返回
we get back or what's the maximum depth or
结果的数量 或最大深度、
maximum magnitude, minimum depth, minimum magnitude and so on.
最大震级、最小深度、 最小震级等
So, let's try this out in a browser and see what comes back.
接下来 我们到浏览器中试一试 看看会返回什么内容
Let's say, I want to get a list of earthquakes for the past day.
例如 我想要获取有关 昨天发生地震的列表
I'm going to type in this URL, add the query method and
我要键入此 URL  添加查询方法
then I'm going to add parameters for the start time and the end time.
然后 添加关于开始时间到 结束时间的参数
So, here I've used the dates 2016-05-02, and
在这里 我使用的日期是 2016-05-02 和
2016-05-03, so that these dates are just one day apart.
2016-05-03  让两个日期相隔仅一天
And it's using a very specific format, year dash month dash day.
使用的是非常具体的格式 年 - 月 - 日
Then finally, I'm going to add format=geojson.
最后 添加 format=geojson
The reason why I'm adding this is because JSON is a pretty good format for
为什么要添加这个呢？因为 JSON 这种格式是非常适合
working with API data and GeoJSON is special type of JSON that is tailored
与 API 数据一同使用的 而 GeoJSON 是 JSON 的一种特殊类型
just for describing geographical information.
专门用于描述 地理相关信息
We'll discuss JSON in detail later in this course.
稍后 我们会在本课程中 详细介绍 JSON
Now, let's press Enter and see what comes back.
现在 按下 Enter 键 观察返回内容
Cool, it gave me a bunch of code.
非常好 返回了这么多代码
It doesn't look all that readable yet in its current state, but
以目前的状态来看 可读性 还不是很高 但是
we can use a formatting tool effect setup a bit.
我们可以使用格式工具效果 来进行一些设置
If I copy and paste this code into JSON pretty printer,
把这些代码复制粘贴到 JSON pretty printer 中
I can get something way more readable.
就可以得到可读性更高的代码
So I paste my code in, I'm going to click the button and there.
那么 我将代码粘贴到这里 然后单击按钮 好了
That's way easier to read.
这样读起来容易多了
Immediately, I can see that the earthquake events are group into nodes
可以一目了然地看到地震事件 经过分组 组成了多个称为
called features and I can see for a given feature like what the magnitude
features 的节点 对于某给定的 feature 可以看到震级
is and a place and the time.
地点和时间
By the way, that's an interesting way to represent time.
顺便说一下 这里用来表达时间 的方式很特别
This is actually called Unix timestamp.
事实上 这种方式称为 Unix 时间戳
Computers often use Unix timestamps, because they are integers.
计算机一般都会使用 Unix 时间戳 因为它是整数
And therefore, they're easy to work with when doing calculations between two
因此无论是两个日期之间的计算 或者其他类型的数学运算
dates or any other kind of math operation.
使用整数相对而言 都比较容易
A Unix timestamp, by the way is defined as the number of seconds
Unix 时间戳是根据自 1970 年 1 月 1 日开始经过的
since the date January 1st, 1970.
秒数来定义的
By the way, don't worry when you have to display a date and time in software.
顺便说一下 要在软件中显示日期和时间 也无需担心
There's plenty of libraries and
还有很多库和
other ways to represent that in a more human readable way.
其他方法可以提供可读性更高 的方式来表达日期和时间
I can also see from this list that the magnitude values are often very low.
从列表中可以看出 通常 震级的值非常低
Nobody is going to fee a 0.1 earthquake.
0.1 级地震大家是感觉不到的
In fact, let's assume we only care about earthquakes that are magnitude of 4.5 or
我们假设只关注 4.5 或以上震级的
higher.
地震
What query parameter would we add to the URL to make this only show me
那么 我们应该在 URL 中添加什么查询参数 才能只显示
those larger quakes?
那些较大规模的地震呢？
After a quick glance at the documentation, I can see that min
在快速浏览文档后 我发现
magnitude will give me events that are larger than the indicated value,
使用 magnitude 可以返回 大于指定值的事件
so let's put that in.
所以输入 magnitude
Now, I'll go ahead and grab all this code and
现在 我要继续 选中全部代码
paste it back into JSON pretty print.
把代码粘贴到 JSON pretty print 中
And now, let's take a look at what we have.
现在 我们来看看 具体有哪些内容
And indeed, right away, I can see a magnitude 4.7 earthquake.
果然 我直接可以看到 震级 4.7 的地震
Let's scroll down.
向下滚动
There's a 4.5, a 4.6.
看到 4.5、4.6
And yet, another 4.6.
另一个 4.6
So, this seems to be working as advertised.
看来这正是 想要的效果
Awesome.
非常好
How else might you be able to modify the URL?
还可以对 URL 进行 何种修改呢？
Now, it's time for
现在 轮到你
you to take a look at the documentation and explore things on your own.
来阅读文档 独立 探索发现了
In this table, write in your own words what you think is a good description for
在这张表格中 用自己的话 为列出的各个参数
each of the parameters listed.
写出恰当描述
Use the link to the datafeed in the class notes to get some
使用课堂讲义中的数据 输入链接 获取
USGS earthquake data.
USGS 地震数据
Throw it into a formatter, if you like and
根据偏好 可以将其放入 格式化程序中
give it your best guess as to what you think each data type is used for.
然后猜一猜 每种数据类型的 用途都是什么